Alumni Memorabilia; Collection ua801.004
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Class of 1964, 1960-2014; 1964
  During its time on campus, the Class of 1964 witnessed numerous changes. The school name changed from State University of New York College of Education at Albany (September 1, 1959 - October 16, 1961) to the State University of New York College at Albany (October 16, 1961 - August, 1962) to the State University of New York at Albany (August 1962 - Fall 1986). The groundbreaking ceremony for construction on the new Uptown Campus was held in August 1962. In September 1962 the school admitted its first freshmen non-teacher preparatory students as candidates for bachelor of arts degrees in Liberal Arts and Sciences. The 1963 yearbook was the first to be named the Torch. The school newspaper State College News became the State University News in February 1963 and the Albany Student Press in February 1964. In addition, one of the most noticeable changes was the assessment of tuition for the first time in the Fall of 1963. This event and related student protests are chronicled in the yearbooks and Class of 1964 Senior Record.
  Nearly 600 undergraduate students received their bachelor's degrees from President Evan R. Collins at the New York State College for Teachers on Sunday morning June 14, 1964 at Thurlow Terrace. Buell G. Gallagher, president of City College of New York, served as the commencement speaker.
  This series contains class directories, event programs, school mascots, attire, student handbooks and yearbooks. Of special interest are the many files related to the incoming student/freshman experience including Frosh Week programs and bulletins. Class members Robert Fairbanks, Evelyn J. Petrick and Mary Young Osielski contributed the majority of memorabilia.
  - Admissions Correspondence for Evelyn J. Petrick, 1960 March 11-1960 April 29 (Box 1 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 1)
  - Welcome Frosh Pajama Party, Brubacher Hall, 1960 September 29 (Box 1 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 1)
  - Class of 1964 Welcome to Frosh Week Program, 1960 September (Box 1 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 3)
  - "Hi Frosh" Bulletin, 1960 September (Box 1 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 4)
  - Freshman "Warning" for Not Carrying Matches, 1960 October 09 (Box 1 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 5)
  - "Arms and the Man" Ticket, 1960 October 19 (Box 1 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 6)
  - "Blue Hawaii" Program, Brubacher Formal, 1960 November 05 (Box 1 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 7)
  - "Class of 1964 Presents 'Heaven Only Knows'" Program, 1960 November 12 (Box 1 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 8)
  - Student Christian Association, 9th Annual Christmas Sing Program, 1960 December 18 (Box 1 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 9)
  - Class of 1964, College Handbook for the Yellow Jackets, 1960 (Box 1 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 10)
  - Photograph of Carol Blackwell Lindhurst, Nancy Tully Goldfarb, Corky Petrick, F1 Corroridor, Brubacher Hall, 1960 (Box 1 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 11)
  - Class of 1964 Freshman Beanies, 1960 (Artifact-box 1)
  - Western Civilizations Textbook, 1960 (Oversized 2)
  - Albany City Brochure, ca. 1960 (Box 1 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 12)
  - Correspondence to Incoming Freshman, 1960; Undated (Box 1 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 13)
  - State University of New York College of Education at Albany Directory, 1960-1962 (Box 1 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 14)
  - Mary Young's Course Schedules, 1960-1963; Undated (Box 1 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 15)
  - Mary Young's Student Association Cards, 1960-1964 (Box 1 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 16)
  - State College Revue Presents "The King and I" Program, 1961 March 24-1961 March 25 (Box 1 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 17)
  - Freshmen Class Banquet Program, 1961 March 29 (Box 1 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 18)
  - "Follow Me!" The Moving Up Day Skit Program, 1961 May 06 (Box 1 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 19)
  - Moving Up Day Program, 1961 May 06 (Box 1 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 20)
  - State College News, 1961 May 06 (Box 1 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 21)
  - "Ye Ole Yeller" and "Soph Extra" Newsletters, 1961 September 29-1961 October 14 (Box 1 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 22)
  - Homecoming Varsity Soccer, State vs. Plattsburg Program, 1961 October 14 (Box 1 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 23)
  - "Class of 1964 Presents 'The III Man Scheme'" Program, 1961 November 11 (Box 1 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 24)
  - "Hells Belle" Program, Class of 1965 Campus Night Skit, 1961 November 11 (Box 1 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 25)
  - Diocesan Newman Inter-Club Dinner, 1961 December 03 (Box 1 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 26)
  - Correspondence about Unexcused Absence, 1961 December 06 (Box 1 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 27)
  - Class of 1965 College Handbook for the Red Devils, 1961 (Box 1 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 28)
  - An Introduction to Library Science Textbook, 1961 (Box 1 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 29)
  - Living with Books Textbook, 1963 (Oversized 2)
  - Pedagogue Yearbook, 1961 (Box 1 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 30)
  - Class of 1964 Upperclass Yellow Hat, ca. 1961 (Artifact-box 1)
  - Brubacher Hall Association Program, 1961-1962 (Box 1 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 31)
  - Brubacher Hall Warnings and Sign-on-Return Slips, 1961-1962; Undated (Box 1 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 32)
  - Photocopies of Evelyn J. Petrick's Class Portraits, 1961-1962; Undated (Box 1 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 33)
  - Men's Basketball Program, Siena College vs. Albany State, 1962 January 13 (Box 1 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 34)
  - "Students March on Capitol," Tuition Protest Clipping from The Knickerbocker News, 1962 January 16 (Box 1 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 35)
  - David Boroff Article and Student Reaction, 1962 January 18 (Box 1 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 36)
  - Times-Union Clipping of Tuition Protest, 1962 January (Box 1 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 37)
  - Sophomore Class Banquet Program, 1962 March 24 (Box 1 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 38)
  - State College Revue Presents "Kiss Me Kate", 1962 April 12-1962 April 14 (Box 1 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 39)
  - Moving Up Day Program, 1962 May 05 (Box 1 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 40)
  - "Murder in the Cathedral" Program, 1962 November 12-1962 November 17 (Box 1 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 41)
  - Class of 1966 College Handbook for the Blue Jays, 1962 (Box 1 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 42)
  - Handbook for Frosh Week-End Counselors, 1962 (Box 1 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 43)
  - "Hi Frosh" Bulletin, 1962 (Box 1 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 44)
  - Pedagogue Yearbook, 1962 (Box 1 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 45)
  - State University News, 1963 March 29 (Box 1 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 46)
  - Junior Ring Banquet Program, 1963 May 17 (Box 1 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 47)
  - Moving Up Day Program, 1963 May 18 (Box 1 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 48)
  - Requirements for Permanent Teaching Certificates, 1963 September (Box 1 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 49)
  - Dewey Deicmal Classification Textbook, 1963 (Oversized 3)
  - Literature Study in the High Schools Textbook, 1963 (Box 1 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 50)
  - Sears List of Subject Headings Textbook, 1963 (Oversized 3)
  - Senior Record, Class of 1963 Experiences at University (Box 1 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 51)
  - Torch Yearbook, 1963 (Box 1 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 52)
  - State University at Albany Directory, 1963-1964 (Box 1 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 53)
  - State University News Articles Relating History of University, 1963-1964 (Box 1 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 54)
  - SUNYA Degree Application Receipt, 1964 February 10 (Box 1 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 55)
  - Albany Student Press, 1964 May 12; 1964 May 19 (Box 1 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 56)
  - Moving Up Day Program, 1964 May 16 (Box 1 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 57)
  - Times-Union Memorial Supplement, The John F. Kennedys, 1964 May 29 (Flat-file 1)
  - Tickets to President's Reception and Commencement Exercises, 1964 June 13-1964 June 14 (Box 1 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 58)
  - Photocopy of Commencement Exercises Program, 1964 June 14 (Box 1 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 59)
  - Class of 1968 Campus Viewpoint, 1964 (Box 1 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 60)
  - Class Rings, 1964 (Artifact-box 1)
  - Graduating Class of the Milne School, 1964 (Box 1 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 61)
  - Senior Record, Overview of Class of 1964 Experiences (Box 1 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 62)
  - Photocopies of Evelyn J. Petrick's Certificates, 1964; 1970; Undated (Box 1 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 63)
  - Summer Planning Conference Binder, 1964 (Box 1 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 64)
  - Statesmen Group Photograph, ca. 1964 (Box 1 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 65)
  - SUNY Validation and Activity Card, ca. 1964 (Box 1 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 66)
  - Student ID Cards, 1964-1965 (Box 1 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 67)
  - Memo from Minnie, Association of Women Students Handbook, 1964-1965 (Box 1 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 68)
  - Commencement Exercises Tickets, 1965 June 13 (Box 1 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 69)
  - Statesmen Group Photograph from Torch Yearbook, 1965 (Box 1 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 70)
  - Torch Yearbook, 1965 (Box 1 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 71)
  - "Something New in College Campuses,"U.S. News World Report Article about the University at Albany, 1967 (Box 1 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 72)
  - Alumni Association Correspondence from Class of 1964 Class Councillor, 1980 (Box 1 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 73)
  - Class of 1964 35th Reunion, 1999 June 04-1999 June 06 (Box 1 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 74)
  - Class of 1964 50th Reunion Programs, Invitation and Planning Documents, 2013-2014 (Box 1 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 75)
  - Albany State College for Teachers Sweatshirt, Undated (Oversized 1)
  - Brubacher Hall Matchbook, Undated (Box 2 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 1)
  - Class of 1964 Yellow Sash, Undated (Oversized 1)
  - "College of the Empire State" Alma Mater, Undated (Box 2 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 2)
  - Evelyn Petrick Holiday Name Badge, Undated (Box 2 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 3)
  - Holiday Party Program, Undated (Box 2 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 4)
  - Parents' Day Guide Badge for "Corky", Undated (Box 2 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 5)
  - Purple and Gold College and University Stuffed Animal Mascots, Undated (Artifact-box 2)
  - SUCA Class of 1964 Yellow Jackets Badge, Undated (Box 2 (1964-Class of 1964), Folder 6)
- Class of 1965, 1960-2005, Undated; 1965
  The items donated by the Class of 1965 include programs from plays and later reunions, class newsletters and event lists, a University Directory and some photographs. Also included is two plates celebrating the 50th Anniversary of the Potter Club.
  - Unidentified photograph of a Homcoming Parade, Alumni Quad, ca. 1960 (Box 1 (1965-Class of 1965), Folder 1)
  - Satan's Scroll vol. 1 no. 1, 1961 September 29 (Box 1 (1965-Class of 1965), Folder 2)
  - "Welcome to Frosh Week" Schedule, 1961 September 8-22 (Box 1 (1965-Class of 1965), Folder 3)
  - Satan's Scroll vol. 1 no. 2, 1961 October 6 (Box 1 (1965-Class of 1965), Folder 4)
  - Satan's Scroll vol. 1 no. 3, 1961 October 13 (Box 1 (1965-Class of 1965), Folder 5)
  - The Mistress of the Inn - program, 1964 July 22-25 (Box 1 (1965-Class of 1965), Folder 6)
  - Doctor Faustus - program, 1964 October 9-14 (Box 1 (1965-Class of 1965), Folder 7)
  - Mata and Hari - program, 1964 December 1 (Box 1 (1965-Class of 1965), Folder 8)
  - Jack and the Beanstalk and Stars on Strings - program, 1964 December 5 (Box 1 (1965-Class of 1965), Folder 9)
  - University Directory, 1964-1965 (Box 1 (1965-Class of 1965), Folder 10)
  - Ethan Frome - program, 1965 February 26-27; 1965 March 1-6 (Box 1 (1965-Class of 1965), Folder 11)
  - Hamlet - program, 1965 April 6 (Box 1 (1965-Class of 1965), Folder 12)
  - New York State Community Theater Journal - vol. 5, no. 2, 1965 April (Box 1 (1965-Class of 1965), Folder 13)
  - The Misanthrope - program, 1965 May 28 (Box 1 (1965-Class of 1965), Folder 14)
  - Group photograph of The Statesmen - Nicholas S. Argyros, Carl Sand, E.K. Kehard, J. Pienning, F. Eugene Tobey, and Paul Cochrone, ca. 1965 (Box 1 (1965-Class of 1965), Folder 15)
  - Statesmen - Member of the Class of 1965, ca. 1965 (Box 1 (1965-Class of 1965), Folder 16)
  - Two one-act plays by Murral Schisgal The Tiger, The Typist - program, 1965 (Box 1 (1965-Class of 1965), Folder 17)
  - Unidentified photograph of two students in front of the uptown library, ca. 1965 (Box 1 (1965-Class of 1965), Folder 18)
  - Potter Club Fiftieth Anniversary Plate (1931-1981) (Oversized 1, Item 1)
  - Potter Club Fiftieth Anniversary Plate (1931-1981) (Oversized 1, Item 2)
  - 25th Reunion Program, 1990 June 9 (Box 1 (1965-Class of 1965), Folder 19)
  - 35th Reunion Program, 2000 June 10 (Box 1 (1965-Class of 1965), Folder 20)
  - 40th Reunion Program, 2005 June 4 (Box 1 (1965-Class of 1965), Folder 21)
- Class of 1966, 1944-1991; 1966; 1.03 cubic ft.
  The items donated by the Class of 1966 include programs from plays, class newsletters and event lists, University Directories, class beanies, and some photographs.
  - "Hi Frosh" Booklet, 1962 (Box 1 (1966-Class of 1966), Folder 1)
  - Statesmen: 1965 at NY World's Fair (Box 1 (1966-Class of 1966), Folder 2)
  - The Carillon Presentation - Alumni Day Program, 1966 June 18 (Box 1 (1966-Class of 1966), Folder 3)
  - "Louie, Louie" Paper Record, and "Class of 1966" Lettering, Undated (Box 1 (1966-Class of 1966), Folder 4)
  - Albany State Penant Stickers, 1966 (Box 1 (1966-Class of 1966), Folder 5)
  - SUNYA Directory, 1965 (Box 1 (1966-Class of 1966), Folder 6)
  - Invitation to Evan Revere Collins Circle Dedication Ceremony, 1991 (Box 1 (1966-Class of 1966), Folder 7)
  - Fiddler on the Roof Playbill, 1966 January (Box 1 (1966-Class of 1966), Folder 8)
  - Editorial about College Reunions- "La plus ca Change, Undated (Box 1 (1966-Class of 1966), Folder 9)
  - Newspaper Clipping-"By Whom the Bell Tolls", Undated (Box 1 (1966-Class of 1966), Folder 10)
  - Photograph of Peterkin-1991 Distinguished Alumni Award Recipient (Box 1 (1966-Class of 1966), Folder 11)
  - Project Carillon Papmphlet, ca. 1966 (Box 1 (1966-Class of 1966), Folder 12)
  - Nostalgia 101-Memories of 1962-1966, Undated (Box 1 (1966-Class of 1966), Folder 13)
  - Albany Ahtletic Letter, Undated (Box 1 (1966-Class of 1966), Folder 14)
  - Social Calendars, 1962-1966 (Box 1 (1966-Class of 1966), Folder 15)
  - Campus Viewpoint, 1963 (Box 1 (1966-Class of 1966), Folder 16)
  - University Guidelines, 1963 September 1 (Box 1 (1966-Class of 1966), Folder 17)
  - Memo from Minnie, 1963 (Box 1 (1966-Class of 1966), Folder 18)
  - Campus Viewpoint, 1964 September 1 (Box 1 (1966-Class of 1966), Folder 19)
  - Spring Primer, 1966 January (Box 1 (1966-Class of 1966), Folder 20)
  - Patch with University Seal, Undated (Box 1 (1966-Class of 1966), Folder 21)
  - Junior Class Extra, 1964 November 9-1963 May 18 (Box 1 (1966-Class of 1966), Folder 22)
  - Basketball Programs, ca.1963-1965 (Box 2 (1966-Class of 1966), Folder 1)
  - Performance Playbills and Photographs, ca.1963-1966 (Box 2 (1966-Class of 1966), Folder 2)
  - Brochures and Pamphlets, ca. 1963-1965 (Box 2 (1966-Class of 1966), Folder 3)
  - College of the Empire State Centennial History, ca. 1944 (Box 2 (1966-Class of 1966), Folder 4)
  - Suppression- A Weekly Journal, 1962 October-1967 April (Box 2 (1966-Class of 1966), Folder 5)
  - University Bulletins and Newsletters, 1962 October-1967 April (Box 2 (1966-Class of 1966), Folder 6)
  - Jay's Journal, 1962 October 5-1963 October 4 (Box 2 (1966-Class of 1966), Folder 7)
  - Satan's Scroll, 1962 October 5-1962 October 26 (Box 2 (1966-Class of 1966), Folder 8)
  - Gremlin Gazette, 1963 May 18 (Box 2 (1966-Class of 1966), Folder 9)
  - Gnome's News, 1963 October 4-1963 October 25 (Box 2 (1966-Class of 1966), Folder 10)
  - The Waterbury Knozes, 1962 November 21 (Box 2 (1966-Class of 1966), Folder 11)
  - Student Senate Records, 1963 October 7-1964 October 14 (Box 2 (1966-Class of 1966), Folder 12)
  - Papers of Various Student Organizations, ca. 1963-1965 (Box 2 (1966-Class of 1966), Folder 13)
  - Inter-Fraternity Council, 1963 March-1964 April (Box 2 (1966-Class of 1966), Folder 14)
  - Class of 1966 Beanie, Undated (Box 3 (1966-Class of 1966), Folder 1)
  - Class of 1967 Beanie, Undated (Box 3 (1966-Class of 1966), Folder 2)
  - Class of 1966 Beanie, Undated (Box 3 (1966-Class of 1966), Folder 3)
- Class of 1967, 1962-1969; 1967
  More than 650 men and women received their degrees from President Evan R. Collins at the State University of New York at Albany on Sunday morning June 11, 1967. U.S. Senator Jacob K. Javits delivered the commencement address to a class in transition in many ways. During the Class of 1967's years on campus, enrollment increased dramatically reaching a then all-time high of 7,094 in the Fall of 1966, the Uptown Campus was built and the University rented any available space it could locate to temporarily hold classes during the building process. The Uptown Campus officially opened during the group's final year of studies, students moved into new dorms and the Class of 1967 began using new facilities like the Campus Center. Old policies and traditions, including a curfew for women students and the wearing of the freshman beanie, were being laid to rest. The class helped usher in new student traditions, such as Telethon which became a popular 24 hour fund-raising event to benefit the New York State Mental Health Association, Inc. started in October 1966.
  Henry M. Madej, BA 1967, is the main contributor to this class' collection and an active member of the Albany community. He is a member of the University Alumni Association and the Pine Hills Neighborhood Association. Please see the Henry M. Madej Papers, APAP-140, for more information.
  This series is divided into administrative records and special events.
  - Administrative Records, 1963-1968; 1967.1
    This series contains Central Council minutes, agendas, constitutions, and other student government files. In addition, there is student services correspondence, housing, tuition, and other academic information. These records form a solid representation of the information that students received or created about themselves over the course of their education at the State University of New York at Albany.
    - Student Services Records, 1963-1966 (Box 1 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 1)
    - Academic Records, 1964-1965 (Box 1 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 2)
    - Housing and Tuition Payments, 1964-1967 (Box 1 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 3)
    - Housing Records, 1964-1967 (Box 1 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 4)
    - Class Schedules and Grade Cards, 1964-1968 (Box 1 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 5)
    - Central Council Constitution, 1965-1966 (Box 1 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 6)
    - Central Council Constitutions, Bills, and Organization, 1965-1966 (Box 1 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 7-8)
    - Central Council Correspondence, Minutes, and Agendas, 1965-1966 (Box 1 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 9-10)
    - Central Council Finances and Miscellaneous, 1965-1966 (Box 1 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 11)
    - Student Government Materials, 1966 (Box 1 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 12)
    - Central Council Bills and Organization, 1966-1967 (Box 1 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 13-14)
    - Central Council Constitution, 1966-1967 (Box 1 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 15)
    - Central Council Finances and Miscellaneous, 1966-1967 (Box 1 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 16-17)
    - Central Council Minutes, 1966-1967 (Box 1 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 18-20)
  - Special Activities and Events, 1962-1969; 1967.2
    This series contains student activity photographs, invitations, events cards, directories, guidelines, and publications. In addition to these items, there are artistic representations of the University campuses in photographs, prints, and watercolors, providing a clearer picture of the campus in many stages of its development.
    - Saturday Review Issues with University Mentioned, 1962 January 20; 1964 April 18 (Box 1 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 21)
    - Miscellaneous Newspaper Clippings and Student Information, 1962-1967 (Box 1 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 22)
    - Class of 1967 Freshman Week Schedule, 1963 (Box 1 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 23)
    - Freshman Acceptance and Registration Information, 1963 (Box 1 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 24)
    - Freshman Guidelines, Events, and News, 1963 Fall (Box 1 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 25)
    - Campus Viewpoint Cover Photocopy, 1963-1964 (Box 1 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 26)
    - Class of 1967 Hi, Frosh! Guide, 1963-1964 (Box 1 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 27)
    - Memo from Minnie Cover Photocopy, 1963-1964 (Box 1 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 28)
    - Student Guidelines, 1963-1964 (Box 1 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 29)
    - SUNY Albany Directory, 1963-1964 (Box 1 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 30)
    - University Guidelines Cover Photocopy, 1963-1964 (Box 1 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 31)
    - Waterbury Dorm Hall Photograph, 1963-1964 (Box 1 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 32)
    - Waterbury Hall Handbook for Men's Residence, 1963-1964 (Box 1 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 33)
    - Albany Student Press, 1963-1966 (Oversized 1-3)
    - Sundry Campus Entertainment Tickets and Programs, 1963-1966 (Box 1 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 34)
    - Alumni Quad Photographs, 1963-1967 (Box 1 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 35)
    - Statesmen Photograph, ca. 1964 (Box 1 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 36)
    - Primer, 1964 Spring (Box 1 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 37)
    - Green Gremlin Informal Pizza Party Tickets, 1964 May 15 (Box 1 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 38)
    - Student Guidelines, 1964-1965 (Box 1 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 39)
    - SUNY Albany Directory, 1964-1965 (Box 1 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 40)
    - Student Activity Cards, 1964-1967 (Box 1 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 41)
    - Campus Viewpoint, 1965 (Box 2 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 1)
    - Primer, 1965 (Box 2 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 2)
    - Statesmen Photographs, 1965 (Box 2 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 3)
    - Student Budget Cut Protest, 1965 April (Box 2 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 4)
    - Student Leaders Reception Invitation, 1965 December (Box 2 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 5)
    - Primer, 1965 Fall-1966 (Box 2 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 6)
    - SUNY Albany Directory, 1965 Fall-1966 (Box 2 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 7)
    - Campus Viewpoint, 1966 (Box 2 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 8)
    - Primer, 1966 Spring (Box 2 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 9)
    - Sigma Phi Sigma Sin-cerely Yours Issue, 1966 May 31 (Box 2 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 10)
    - Memo from Minnie Handbook for Women Students, 1966-1967 (Box 2 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 11)
    - Primer, 1966-1967 (Box 2 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 12)
    - Student Guidelines, 1966-1967 (Box 2 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 13)
    - SUNY Albany Directory, 1966-1967 (Box 2 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 14)
    - Sigma Phi Sigma Dinner Mementos, ca. 1966 (Box 2 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 15)
    - Sigma Phi Sigma Formal Dinner Invitations, 1966 March 16; 1966 April 13 (Box 2 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 16)
    - Observation, 1967 Spring (Box 2 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 17)
    - Primer, 1967 Spring (Box 2 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 18)
    - The Word, 1967 March (Box 2 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 19)
    - Senator Robert F. Kennedy Posters, 1967 March 18 (Oversized 4, Folder 1)
    - Senator Robert F. Kennedy Tickets, 1967 March 18 (Box 2 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 20)
    - Senator Robert F. Kennedy Event Materials Photograph, 1967 March 18 (Box 2 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 21)